const questions = [
{
	questionNumber: 1,
	question: 'What all female band was closely related to and occasionally played with "Thee Headcoats"?',
	answerOne: 'Broadcast',
	answerTwo: 'Hinds',
	answerThree: 'Moving Panoramas',
	answerFour: 'Thee Headcoatees',
	correctAnswer: 'Thee Headcoatees'
},
{
	questionNumber: 2,
	question: 'What is the lead singer of the Pixies birth name?',
	answerOne: 'Frank Black',
	answerTwo: 'Black Francis',
	answerThree: 'Charles Michael Kittridge Thompson IV',
	answerFour: 'Dave Philips',
	correctAnswer: 'Charles Michael Kittridge Thompson IV'
},
{
	questionNumber: 3,
	question: "On the Sex Pistols studio album ‘Never Mind the Bollocks, Here's the Sex Pistols’ what was the only song that Sid Vicious recorded?",
	answerOne: 'Bodies',
	answerTwo: 'God Save the Queen',
	answerThree: 'Pretty Vacant',
	answerFour: 'Holidays in the Sun',
	correctAnswer: 'Holidays in the Sun'
},
{
	questionNumber: 4,
	question: "In what city was the video for The Clash song ‘Rock the Casbah’ recorded?",
	answerOne: "New York",
	answerTwo: "Chicago",
	answerThree: "London",
	answerFour: "Austin",
	correctAnswer: "Austin"
},
{
	questionNumber: 5,
	question: "What influential 70s punk band recently toured for their 40 year anniversary?",
	answerOne: "The Damned",
	answerTwo: "Circle Jerks",
	answerThree: "X",
	answerFour: "Bad Brains",
	correctAnswer: "X"
},
{
	questionNumber: 6,
	question: "What was the first band that Nick Cave was the frontman for?",
	answerOne: "Nick Cave and the Bad Seeds",
	answerTwo: "The Birthday Party",
	answerThree: "Grinderman",
	answerFour: "Nick Cave",
	correctAnswer: "The Birthday Party"
},
{
	questionNumber: 7,
	question: "What is the name of the lead singer of the band The Dead Boys?",
	answerOne: "Cheetah Chrome",
	answerTwo: "Jonny Blitz",
	answerThree: "Jimmy Zero",
	answerFour: "Gene O’Connor",
	correctAnswer: "Cheetah Chrome"
},
{
	questionNumber: 8,
	question: "What year did Clash frontman Joe Strummer die?",
	answerOne: "2002",
	answerTwo: "2012",
	answerThree: "2008",
	answerFour: "2004",
	correctAnswer: "2002"
},
{
	questionNumber: 9, 
	question: "What was the title of the Damned’s first album?",
	answerOne: "Damned Damned Damned",
	answerTwo: "Strawberries",
	answerThree: "The Black Album",
	answerFour: "Music for Pleasure",
	correctAnswer: "Damned Damned Damned"
},
{
	questionNumber: 10,
	question: "What is the name of Leonard Cohen’s last album?",
	answerOne: "Songs of Love and Hate",
	answerTwo: "Popular Problems",
	answerThree: "Songs from a Room",
	answerFour: "You Want it Darker",
	correctAnswer: "You Want it Darker"
}
]

/*add answers here in nested array*/ 